Guide to the Stanford University, Graduate School of Business, Oral History Collection SC0659
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Graduate School of Business, oral history collection
1974-1999
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Graduate School of Business
SC0659
0.75 Linear Feet
Interviews on the history of Stanford's business school conducted with professors Arjay Miller, Harold J. Leavitt, James T. S. Porterfield, Gerald M. Meier, Ezra Solomon, Robert K. Jaedicke, Charles T. Horngren, James E. Howell, Charles P.Bonini, and Thomas W. Harrell. Specific topics covered include its various deans, particularly Ernest Arbuckle; financial history; curriculum; ICAME (International Center for the Advancement of Management Education); Public Management Program; and women students and faculty.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Administrative transfer, 2001.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Interviews on the history of Stanford's business school conducted with professors Arjay Miller, Harold J. Leavitt, James T. S. Porterfield, Gerald M. Meier, Ezra Solomon, Robert K. Jaedicke, Charles T. Horngren, James E. Howell, Charles P.Bonini, and Thomas W. Harrell. Specific topics covered include its various deans, particularly Ernest Arbuckle; financial history; curriculum; ICAME (International Center for the Advancement of Management Education); Public Management Program; and women students and faculty.
Stanford University. Graduate School of Business. History; Stanford University. Graduate School of Business. Public Management Program; Porterfield, James T. S. (James Temple Starke).; Howell, James Edwin.; Solomon, Ezra.; Meier, Gerald M.; Harrell, Thomas W. (Thomas Willard); Miller, Arjay.; Bonini, Charles P.; Jaedicke, Robert K.; Arbuckle, Ernest C.; Spurr, William A.; Leavitt, Harold J.; Wentworth, Gerald; Jaedicke, Robert K.; Horngren, Charles T.; Leavitt, Harold J.; Howell, James Edwin.; Meier, Gerald M.; Bonini, Charles P.; Miller, Arjay.; Stanford University. Graduate School of Business; Solomon, Ezra.; Arbuckle, Ernest C.; Stanford University. Graduate School of Business; Spurr, William A.; Troxell, John P.; Troxell, John P.; Stanford University. International Center for the Advancement of Management Education
- Transcripts
  - James Howell, Charles Bonini, Tom Harrell, 1999 Jun 29 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Harold Leavitt, James Porterfield, Gerry Meier, 1999 Jul 7 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arjay Miller, 1999 Aug 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ezra Solomon, Bob Jaedicke, Chuck Horngren, 1999 Jun 17 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Videotapes
  - Arjay Miller, 1999 Aug 11; 3 videotape(s) (betacam) (Box 2)
  - Bob Jaedicke, Ezra Solomon, Chuck Horngren, 1999 Jun 17; 3 videotape(s) (betacam) (Box 2)
  - Harold Leavitt, James Porterfield, Gerry Meier, 1999 Jul 7; 3 videotape(s) (betacam) (Box 2)
  - James Howell, Charles Bonini, Tom Harrell, 1999 Jun 29; 3 videotape(s) (betacam) (Box 2)
- Audiotapes
  - Remele, Carol, 1974-10-02; 2.8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Holder, Paul, 1974 Oct 13; 2.9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Spurr, William A., 1974 Oct 17; 2.5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Troxell, John P., 1974 Oct 17; 2.6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Dougall, Herbert, 1974 Oct 23; 2.10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Faville, Mrs. David, 1974 Oct 23; 2.11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kreps, Ted, 1974 Nov 6; 2.12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Wentworth, Gerald, 1974 Nov 18; 2.7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kroeger, Arthur, 1974 Nov 14; 2.13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)